coderbyte.com 2019-06-16

# Coderbyte

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of Coderbyte Enterprise Inc ("we," "our," or "us") on the collection, use, and disclosure of your information on www.coderbyte.com and the services, features, content, applications, and products we offer (the "Site" or "Coderbyte"). 

Your privacy is important to us. When running Coderbyte, we follow a few fundamental principles: 

  * We don't ask you for personally identifiable information (defined below) unless we truly need it. That being said, what we do ask for is solely to enable us to build an amazing customized experience and to communicate with you.
  * We don't share your information with third parties except to deliver you the Site, comply with the law, make Coderbyte better, protect our rights, or effectuate a business transfer.
  * We're not a huge, faceless corporation. We're just normal people trying to deliver an incredible experience. If you have any questions or concerns about this policy, please reach out to us at _[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_.

**How You Accept This Policy**

By using Coderbyte, creating a user account, or purchasing services through the Site, you agree to the use, disclosure, and procedures outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

**What Information Does Coderbyte Collect?**

The information we collect from you falls into two categories: (i) personally identifiable information (i.e., data that could potentially identify you as an individual) ("Personal Information"), and (ii) non-personally identifiable information (i.e., information that cannot be used to identify who you are) ("Non-Personal Information"). This Privacy Policy covers both categories and will tell you how we might collect and use each type. 

We may collect a variety of Personal Information, including:

  * Information from Third Party Services (defined below) that you explicitly give us access to;
  * Your contact information, such as your phone number, social media handle, or email address (depending on how you contact us); and
  * Your credit card information (although we use a third party payment processor, as described below) and billing address.

We may also collect a variety of Non-Personal Information, including: 

Various analytics data, such as: (i) the IP address of the computer you use to access the Site; (ii) the type of browser software you are using; (iii) the operating system you are using; (iv) the date and time you access or use the Site; (v) the website address, if any, that linked you to our Site; (vi) the website address, if any, you leave our website and travel to; and (vii) other non-personally identifiable traffic data; and 

Any screen name or username you create, as well as any photos that you upload and associate with your account on Coderbyte. 

**How We Collect Information**

When You Create a Profile or Provide Us with Information to Purchase a Membership Subscription 

If you create a profile or purchase services on our Site, we may request certain Personal Information. This may include contact information such as your name, organization, email address, phone number, and billing address. You also have the option to provide us with information about your social media accounts, such as your Twitter or Github handle or a link to your LinkedIn profile. 

We, or companies that provide services on our behalf, may also collect certain financial information from you, such as your payment method (which may include a valid credit card number, type, expiration date, or other financial information). By making a purchase through Coderbyte, you give us consent to use and provide your financial information as we consider necessary to process the transaction. 

**Information We Automatically Collect**

Like most websites, Coderbyte may incorporate technology such as "pixel tags," "web beacons," and "cookies." Pixel tags or web beacons are tracking devices on websites or in emails that can monitor the behavior of the user visiting the website or sending the e-mail. Cookies (not to be confused with the sugary treat) are small files that web servers may place on your computer when you visit a website. 

Here at Coderbyte, we use cookies to help identify and track usage of the Site and to make it easier to deliver a personalized experience. You can easily refuse our cookies by adjusting the preferences in your browser. However, be forewarned that disabling cookies may cause Coderbyte to not operate properly. 

In order to improve and grow Coderbyte, we also use analytics tools, such as Google Analytics, to automatically collect information about user and visitor usage (collectively "Analytics Tools"). These Analytics Tools collect data such as how often you visit Coderbyte, what areas of the Site you visit, and what other sites or services you used prior to using Coderbyte. 

Analytics Tools generally operate differently. For example, Google Analytics only collects the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit Coderbyte, not your name or other identifying information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your computer to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. As of right now, we only use the information we get from Analytics Tools to improve Coderbyte and do not combine the information collected through the use of Analytics Tools with personally identifiable information. However, we reserve the right to do so in the future.

Please note Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your use of Coderbyte is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Service and the [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to Coderbyte by disabling cookies on your browser. You also can opt out of Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

**Third Party Services**

We haven't built all of the features offered on Coderbyte from scratch. To run the Site, we often utilize various third-party products (collectively "Third Party Services"), such as Facebook, Instagram, and Twitter. If you authorize us to connect with these Third Party Services, you grant us permission to collect certain Personal Information, such as your name, email address, phone number, and any other information that the Third Party Service makes available to us. Please note that your use of these Third Party Services is governed by their respective Terms of Service and Privacy Policies. We use and disclose any collected information in accordance with our own Privacy Policy. 

**Communications You Initiate with Us**

We do everything possible to make sure you have an amazing experience when using Coderbyte. If you contact us in person, by phone, email, instant message, live chat, social media, or by some other means (either through our Site or through a Third Party Service), we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence for later reference (to help improve our Site!). 

**How We Use the Information We Gather**

We primarily use the information we collect and store to enhance Coderbyte. Except if we sell all or a portion of our business, or as otherwise described below, we do not rent, trade, or sell your Personal Information. 

Use of Information to Provide Coderbyte to You 

We use Personal Information to create an awesome experience. Some ways we may internally use your information are to: 

  * Facilitate the sale of our services;
  * Contact you when necessary;
  * Respond to your comments or questions;
  * Provide you with additional information according to your preferences;
  * Customize and personalize your Coderbyte experience;
  * Generate aggregated statistics to help us improve the customer experience;
  * Make Coderbyte easier and more convenient for you (such as by prepopulating forms when you have already provided identical information);
  * Provide recommendations to you;
  * Send you information and marketing materials about services and products available on our Site;
  * Train our team members; or
  * Other internal business purposes.

**Aggregated Personal Data and Non-Personal Information**

We may share or disclose aggregated Personal Data or Non-Personal Information with service providers or with other persons we conduct business with. These service providers and other persons may also share with us aggregated Non-Personal Information that they have independently developed or acquired. Additionally, we may combine aggregate information from the pixel tags, web beacons, and cookies with similar data we collect from other visitors to help us improve the Site. When doing so, we do our best to ensure that the any aggregated information cannot be linked back to you. 

Except as we discuss in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your Personal Information with third parties who wish to market other products and services to you. 

**Agents or Third Party Partners**

We may provide your Personal Information to our employees, contractors, agents, service providers, and designees ("Agents") to enable them to perform certain services for us exclusively, including:

  * Order fulfillment;
  * Payment processing;
  * Website-related services such as web hosting;
  * Improvement of website-related services and features;
  * Maintenance services; or 
  * Distribution of advertisements and other marketing materials on our behalf.

**Business Transfers**

We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that would be transferred. Also, if we (or our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, your Personal Information could be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party. By accepting this Privacy Policy, as outlined above, you consent to any such transfer. 

Protection of Us and Others 

We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we reasonably believe is necessary to: comply with the law or a court order; cooperate with law enforcement; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Coderbyte, our employees, our users, or others. 

**What Personal Information Can I Access or Change?**

Once you sign up for an account, we provide you with various options that enable you to delete or revise your Personal Information. You can change, alter, or amend Personal Information that you provide to us by visiting your account settings at coderbyte.com/settings/. If you have any questions, feel free to contact us at any time at 

_[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_

. 

If you decide you don't want to receive email or other mail from us, you can select the "opt out" provision in our communications or in your profile settings to unsubscribe. Unsubscribing will stop you from receiving most types of communication, but it may not apply to emails about orders or transactions you place through the Site or to respond to your specific request. 

**Data Retention**

If you delete your account or request that your information be deleted, we still may retain some Personal Information that you have provided to us in order to maintain Coderbyte or to comply with relevant laws. 

**Data Security**

We are committed to making sure your information is protected and have selected third-party vendors, including Stripe and PayPal, that help keep your Personal Information safe. Unfortunately, we do not control these third parties and therefore cannot guarantee complete security. 

We do employ several physical and electronic safeguards to keep your information safe, including encrypted user passwords and securing all connections with industry standard transport layer security. 

If you log into your account on a shared computer, be sure to sign out of your account when finished. If you believe a third party has access to your account, you must let us know as soon as possible. 

Even with all these precautions, we cannot fully guarantee against the access, disclosure, alteration, or deletion of data through events, including but not limited to hardware or software failure or unauthorized use. Any information that you provide to us is done so entirely at your own risk. 

**Children**

We are especially sensitive about children's information. We're not a site targeted towards children, and we don't knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. If you are a parent or legal guardian of a minor child, we will treat any information that you provide us while using Coderbyte on behalf of your minor child as Personal Information as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy. If you have questions concerning our information practices with respect to children, or if you learn that a child under the age of 13 has used Coderbyte, created a user account, or provided us with personal information, please email us at 

_[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_

. 

**Online Tracking and How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals**

Online tracking is the collection of data about an individual's Internet activity used to deliver targeted advertisements and for other purposes. Some web browsers (including Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox, and Chrome) incorporate a "Do Not Track" (DNT) or similar feature that signals to websites that a visitor does not want to have his/her online activity and behavior tracked. If an online service elects to respond to a particular DNT signal, the service may refrain from collecting certain personal information about the browser's user. Not all browsers offer a DNT option and there is currently no industry consensus as to what constitutes a DNT signal. For these reasons, many website operators, including Coderbyte, do not take action to respond to DNT signals. For more information about DNT signals, visit [http://allaboutdnt.com](http://allaboutdnt.com/). 

**We Reserve the Right to Update and Revise This Privacy Policy at Any Time**

We occasionally review this Privacy Policy to make sure it complies with applicable laws and conforms to changes in our business. We may need to update this Privacy Policy, and we reserve the right to do so at any time. If we do revise this Privacy Policy, we will update the "Effective Date" at the bottom of this page so that you can tell if it has changed since your last visit and will do our best to notify you. Please review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are aware of its terms. Any use of Coderbyte after an amendment to our Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance to the revised or amended agreement. 

**Your Rights as a California Resident**

If you are a California resident, in addition to awesome weather, you also get the ability to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of Personal Information we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes and the contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties (under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84). If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to 

_[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_

. We won't even ask you for a bottle of Napa Valley chardonnay in return (but if you send one, our staff will happily accept). 

**International Users and Visitors**

Coderbyte is hosted in the United States. Because the Internet is global, you should note that by providing Personal Information as an international visitor or user, you are: (i) permitting the transfer of your Personal Information to the United States, which may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you reside; and (ii) permitting the use of your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Questions?**

We'd be happy to answer them. Shoot us an email or send us a note: 

Email: 

_[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_

Mailing Address: 

Coderbyte Enterprise Inc  
434 Washington Street  
Carlstadt, NJ 07072 

**Effective Date: April, 19, 2016.**

Thanks for reading our Privacy Policy!
